### **ABOUT ME**

**66** I uphold a diligent work ethic, characterized by resolute determination and an unwavering commitment to continual self-improvement. I am actively pursuing opportunities in analytics implementation engineering, my expertise lies in customer data platforms, tagging, data collection, and automation.

### **TRAINING**

Master in React Udemy May 2023

The Complete JavaScript Course Udemy
May 2022

JS Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp.org May 2021

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp.org Mar 2021

Python for Data Science EDX

Jun 2019

PhD Physical Chemistry University of St Andrews Jun 2018

MSc Chemistry University of Liverpool Jun 2013

+ See More

## **SKILLS**

⟨★⟩ IT: Segment CDP • Rudderstack CDP GTM • GA • JS • React • HTML • CSS SQL • Amplitude • Braze • Python • Numpy Pandas • Scipy • Scikit-learn • Matplotlib Seaborn • Blender • APIs • LaTeX • Git Linux • Matlab/Octave • VBA • Inkscape • Arduino • Raspberry Pi • Maths & Stats

**(DESTRUCTION OF SERVICE AND USE OF SERVICE AND USE** 

+ OTHERS: Publication ● Research ● Spectroscopy ● Oral presentation ● Project Management ● Problem-solving ● Teamwork ● Customer Service ● Driving licence ● First Aid

# CHRISTIAN LARREA

# Implementation Engineer

□ 0752 2140 226 @ crlarrea@protonmail.com ♀ Gibraltar, GI

▶ Web in LinkedIn in Orcid

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Martech Exec - tombola - Gibraltar, GI

Jan 2024 - Presently

- Implemented Hightouch integration with marketing tools, enabling data flow and enrichment
- Configured GTM, deployed tracking pixels and tags for effective data collection.
- Designed and implemented processes and conducted troubleshooting through automated QA.
- Led POC initiatives and implementation of customer data platforms, evaluating their suitability for the organisation's needs.

# Implementation Engineer - Spotlight Sports Group - London, GB

Apr 2022 - Aug 2023

- Managed Segment CDP to collect and unify customer data from various sources, such as websites, apps, databases and CRM systems.
- Configured and troubleshot GTM and GA to capture user behavioural data.
- Developed automated data governance policies for data collection to ensure data accuracy and consistency.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to identify business requirements and translate them into analytics implementation solutions.

#### Jr Implementation Analyst - Spotlight Sports Group - London, GB Sep 2021 - Apr 2022

- Designed and implemented custom JS GTM tags.
- Utilized web scraping techniques to collect data from external websites.
- Collaborated with business stakeholders to design tracking plans that defined the data collection and validation of its accuracy.

#### Programmer - Freelance - Las Palmas, SP

Apr 2020 - Sep 2021

- Developed an intuitive user interface for database querying for end-users to search, filter, and retrieve data.
- Streamlined the generation of invoices from data sources.
- Delivered e-commerce projects that seamlessly integrated shopping carts, payments, and shipping solutions.

#### Data Analyst - XPS Pension Group - Belfast, GB

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

- Handled sensitive financial client data with confidentiality and integrity.
- Developed scripts in VBA for data modelling and visualization to support decision-making and actionable insights.
- Liaised with project management and client teams to understand their data needs.

## Post-doctoral Fellow - Queen's University - Kingston, CA

Sep 2018 - Jan 2019

- Operated and maintained scientific equipment.
- Conducted data collection, modelling, and analysis of spectroscopic data.
- Mentored students and ensured a safe and productive research environment.